you want hormones to be at a steady
state you don't want to Peak and drop we
keep talking about mimicking a circadian
cycle but remember circadian Cycles only
exist because your body has to operate
in a certain mechanism naturally where
it produces things and then it takes a
break and it produces things and it
takes a break we don't start our engines
in our car rev to 5,000 RPM and hold
them there for five years you blow your
engine you drive you turn it off you
drive you turn it off
now when that system breaks and you
decide to start a regimen of exogenous
hormones you no longer need to concern
yourself with breaking the system it's
already broken now you can find this the
level that you feel you're very best and
live there all the time you're receiving
this outside source to replenish what
you've lost we don't need to have ups
and downs anymore that is just your
body's natural way of saying hey I can
go to work all night long making this
great hormone for you and then during
the day as you're using the hormone I'm
going to take a break so tomorrow I can
come back and work again we don't have
to mimic this cycle once we decide to go
on exogenous help
[Music]